## MOMOH HERODION VICTOR MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

09035331649, 08083600310 momohhero2@gmail.com 12 GIDEON OGBONDA STREET, RUMUAGHOLU, RUMUOKORO, PH, RIVERS STATE.

A proficient software developer with experience in developing mobile, desktop, and website applications with Flutter, Nodejs, Java, XML, Flask Framework, and other programming languages.

He excels at major stages of the software development life cycle like coding, debugging, testing, and maintenance. He has advanced skills and knowledge of extensive programming tools with a strong background in math, algorithms, and data processing logic.

Also, an expert who develops innovative and bespoke solutions to help companies reach their goals in different industries.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Napses Technologies Mobile App developer

OCTOBER 2021-Present

Develops great Apps and Web products for clients cut across the globe.

Partners with visionary entrepreneurs to build Market Viable products.

Research and implement problem solving ideas to aid the Artificial intelligence and Machine learning team members.

## Next Counsel Limited Mobile Developer

NOVEMBER 2020- OCTOBER 2021

Developed web applications that improve and implement automation and interaction to increase productivity and efficiency of organisation.

Contribute to the innovation of data driven technology solutions required to kick out inefficiency.

## MADEIND8R LEAD mobile app developer

#### MAY 2021-SEPTEMBER 2021

Develop applications that aid the inclusion of machine learning and artificial intelligence in industries.

Tutor Interns to learn new languages, and also master already known languages.

### Demz Analytics Mobile Developer

APRIL 2021 - MAY 2021

Lagos, Nigeria

Developed an AI application that:

- That creates videos from articles, links and texts.
- Adds voice-over to the generated video.

With the aid of other team members using Flutter native cross platform.

## Kashbase Mobile Developer

JUNE 2021 - AUGUST 2021 Lagos, Nigeria

Developed and deployed a FinTech Application called Kashbase, that inculcates all the features of a standard FInTech app, ranging from wallet system to bill payments.

# FREELANCE Mobile App Developer

MARCH 2020 - MAY 2020

- Developed an Anonymous Social Media application GhostMe, using the cross-platform Flutter framework for front-end, and Laravel framework for the backend.
- Discussed customer requirements and proposed solutions with team members.
- Expertly established and incorporated software programs engineered with the aid of using group and up to date integration/deployment scripts to enhance non-stop integration practices.

## OLOTU TECH INNOVATION HUB Mobile App Developer

DECEMBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Supports the entire application life cycle (concept, design, test, release, support) required for building a successful product.
- Built two fully functional mobile applications for GEROCARE.NG by writing clean codes.
- Creates unit and UI tests to identify malfunctions; debug and troubleshoot to optimize performance.
- Communicates with the product development team to plan and implement new features, and improve already existing features to upgrade user experience.

# M-R INTERNATIONAL Junior Developer / Tutor

JULY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Developed a Tic-Tac-Toe game inculcating the single and multiplayer modes.
- Developed a Smart music player application.
- Tutored Interns in Programming with C# to build desktop and mobile Apps.

# BOWEN UNIVERSITY INNOVATION TEAM Mobile App Developer

JANUARY - JUNE 2019

- Aided the digitalization of Bowen University by the development of a variety of mobile applications for classes, hostels, Gate Attendance, Compliance Unit Application and the Examination Card Application using Smart Cards, Near-Field Communication (NFC) technology.
- Used Java and XML language for mobile app front end development, Laravel for backend development, and PHP to build the API.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BOWEN UNIVERSITY, IWO, OSUN STATE**

B.Sc Computer Science and Information Technology 2015-2019

### **ASCENDING COLLEGE**

Cambridge A-Levels Certificate. 2014-2015

#### **EMMY NORBERTON INT'L SCHOOL**

O-Levels Certificate. 2008-2014

#### STANDARD CHILD DEVELOPMENT CENTER

Qualifications:First School Leaving Certificate. 2002-2008

## INTERNSHIP M-R INTERNATIONAL

### MARCH - SEPTEMBER 2018

Android application development and programming training with C# and Cisco. Certified Networking Associate (CCNA)

#### **SKILLS**

Adaptability

Teamwork

Research

Communication

Empathy

Mobile Application Development.

Web Development

**Desktop Application** 

Flask Framework Flutter

Java

**XML** 

Laravel

PHP

Node js

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Language (Advanced)

#### **REFEREES / CONTACT ADDRESS**

Mr. Salvation Stanley-Kemuel, CEO of AppLegends (07063282099).

Mr. Oladimeji Iyanu Oloyede, Senior Full Stack Developer at Andela (07034402456).

Head of Interns M-R International, Engr. Odili Ifeyinwa Maureen (08036699118).